{"id": "0068rSL9HciTtkUBasGv", "question": "The Natural is a book about Roy Hobbs a natural southpaw boxer who goes on to win the heavyweight title from Boom Boom Mancini.", "answer": ["refutes", "no", "false"]}
{"id": "00d4YQ8B8DgwrWnqu0Dq", "question": "Johnny Depp has been in many successful films, including Black Mass, and is the 10th best paid actor in the world.", "answer": ["supports", "yes", "true"]}
{"id": "03RmV6Vuen8le8o09bm7", "question": "Ken Griffey Jr. was not at his dad's champion games because he had to stay home with a babysitter instead.", "answer": ["refutes", "no", "false"]}
{"id": "04E4TvdS25KGyUxGj68e", "question": "The film High Noon subverts gender norms of the time by having the woman rescue the man.", "answer": ["supports", "yes", "true"]}
{"id": "0DoRhFQRI4v0DTgJNKWZ", "question": "Pedro Alvares Cabral was a nobleman and awarded Knight in the King's Council.", "answer": ["supports", "yes", "true"]}
{"id": "0GHMexlMbBBIxfY7rarP", "question": "There are several theories about which building may have inspired the novel.", "answer": ["supports", "yes", "true"]}
{"id": "0H6MvsSN6Z5jZ0JKKAfP", "question": "The Brandenburg Gate was originally called the peace gate.", "answer": ["supports", "yes", "true"]}
{"id": "0JxADjAVSgouny5Zhpk7", "question": "Goodbye, Mr. Chips' story happens in Canada.", "answer": ["refutes", "no", "false"]}
{"id": "0LahoI6Pl6GCvfWWbVEy", "question": "Katy Perry's debut album was not successful.", "answer": ["supports", "yes", "true"]}
{"id": "0RamjBABgsCMktOnatzd", "question": "Roger Taney was the 10th Supreme Court Justice.", "answer": ["refutes", "no", "false"]}
